[
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q1.question",
    "options": ["questions.seinen.q1.option1","questions.seinen.q1.option2","questions.seinen.q1.option3","questions.seinen.q1.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q2.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q2.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q2.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q2.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q2.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q3.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q3.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q3.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q3.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q3.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q4.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q4.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q4.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q4.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q4.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q5.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q5.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q5.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q5.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q5.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q6.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q6.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q6.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q6.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q6.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q7.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q7.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q7.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q7.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q7.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q8.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q8.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q8.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q8.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q8.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q9.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q9.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q9.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q9.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q9.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q10.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q10.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q10.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q10.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q10.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q11.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q11.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q11.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q11.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q11.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q12.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q12.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q12.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q12.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q12.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q13.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q13.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q13.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q13.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q13.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q14.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q14.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q14.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q14.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q14.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q15.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q15.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q15.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q15.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q15.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q16.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q16.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q16.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q16.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q16.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q17.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q17.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q17.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q17.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q17.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q18.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q18.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q18.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q18.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q18.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q19.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q19.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q19.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q19.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q19.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.seinen.q20.question",
    "options": [
      "questions.seinen.q20.option1",
      "questions.seinen.q20.option2",
      "questions.seinen.q20.option3",
      "questions.seinen.q20.option4"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  }
]
